hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Life podcast my name is Jeremiah
Kowski on this podcast I talk about ways
for coaches trainers and mentors to grow
their businesses and to make more money
online now today I want to talk about
the right ways of using artificial
intelligence in your business I noticed
that a lot of people use it in the wrong
way they think it's supposed to replace
human beings when in fact the truth is
it's supposed to help you it's supposed
to help you do more of what you do best
and so I want to talk about the best
ways that we can in our businesses use
AI for me in my business I use it by
taking an idea that I already have and
then I take the AI and it refines that
idea it makes it better it improves it
it makes it something that I can use
deeper without needing to work so hard
myself for instance I will take
transcripts of sessions that I have and
have the AI analyze the transcripts to
give me ideas for what content to create
I'll have it remix other pieces of
content to come up with additional kinds
of content I'll have it dig deeper into
certain things about the psychology or
the psychographics of my students and
customers and what it does is it lets me
know okay these are the types of people
that you work best with these are the
ones that you want to continue working
with and here's maybe some ideas for
what to create so that people want to
actually work with you and so this gives
me an opportunity to really refine
exactly who who I work with how I work
with them and what produces results
instead of me trying to guess instead of
me just trying to figure it out and so
when you use AI That's one of the ways
that I would recommend using it as this
brainstorming buddy a partner that you
can use to come up with ideas or to
brainstorm you into new ideas that you
have now there's a lot of different
things that you can do with AI from a
from video to audio to
Graphics um
I would focus on keeping it simple in
the beginning using tools like chat GPT
uh to learn but there's some new ones
that are out there um that are really
really great like grock 3 is really good
from X I love using that one for a lot
of different things so just try out
different kinds of AI and see okay what
what's working good for you uh for your
goals for your different purposes and
what you're trying to accomplish and
that'll help you out right there now
don't look to the AI to be the answer
that solves every problem that you have
that that does the work for you CU AI is
not supposed to do all the work for you
okay it's never was intended to do all
the work for you it's supposed to just
be an assistant that helps you come up
with different ideas on your own now if
you're struggling with what do I ask the
AI this is what I love to do is I have
to actually describe what my problem is
what the solution I'm looking for is
into a tool like Gro throw your chat GPT
and actually ask the AI how to ask it
literally the AI will tell you how to
ask it how to prompt it what to say for
anything that you can come up with and
it'll do that very high quality as well
so you're never alone when it comes to
having Ai and wondering is this going to
work if I say it this way or if I post
it this way no the AI itself will
actually help you get out of your own
way
and your own sticking point that you
have right there yourself and
so realize that there's a genius that
you have as a as a person that the AI
can't match can't rival there's a genius
level of knowing your subject matter
knowing how people are going to respond
knowing what people like how do you
express it how do you explain it with
people
that the AI can't do better than you can
and so realize that it's best to lean
into that human aspect that you have and
then the artificial intelligence can
help adjust it tweak it make it a little
bit better but at the end of the day at
the end of the
day uh it's best
to focus
on
what feel feels the most authentic what
feels like me what feels like I'm on the
right path when it comes to doing this
and usually when it comes to Ai and you
really lean into like okay well what
feels good that works really well okay
so don't overthink it don't ever analyze
it you can do a lot of great things with
AI and keep it very simple very short in
the process all right grow your life
everybody and I'll talk soon have a good
one
[Music]
[Applause]